놀라운 발명의 세계
AMAZlNG
DlSCOVERlES
놀라운 발명의 세계에
오신 걸 환영합니다
Welcome, everybody!
Welcome to Amazing Discoveries!
어머! 나온다!
It's on again!
이거 안 보면 안 되니?
Guys, could we please
not watch this?
다들 이런 경험이
있을 거예요
This ever happen to you?
You go to get a glass of milk...
우유 한 잔 마시려면
정말 온 몸을 내던져 열어야하죠
...but these cartons are so
flinging, flanging hard to open!
정말 힘드네요
Boy, you said it, Mike.
무슨 방법이 없을까요?
- There's gotta be a better way.
- There is, Kevin!
물론 있죠, 케빈
제발 보지 말자
-Can we please turn this off?
-No way, Kevin!
안돼, 케빈
우유 아주 쉽게 마실 수 있는
혁신적인 제품이 나왔습니다
What if I told you there's
a new product that guarantees...
... you'll never have to open up
milk cartons again?
우유 따개 2000!
Meet the Milkmaster 2000!
기대가 되지?
-lntrigued?
-You're flinging, flanging right I am!
온몸을 내던질 만큼
기대된다
This is the first time he's used this.
You'll see how easy this is to do.
이 제품은 전에 없던 것으로
사용법도 아주 쉽습니다
해봐요
모든 우유 곽에 가능하죠
-This works in any milk carton.
-Wow, it is easy!
정말 쉽군요
이제 매일 우유를 마실 거예요
Now I can have milk every day.
The One With the Metaphorical Tunnel
요즘엔 재밌는 영화가 없어
It's official.
There are no good movies.
그럼 재미없는 영화라도 보자
So let's go to a bad one,
and make out.
내가 돌아 앉을 테니까
벽이라고 생각해
Perhaps you'd like me to turn
so you can bunny-bump against my back?
안녕
- 안녕
- 어서 와, 잘 됐어?
-Hey, man. What's up?
-Maybe you can tell me.
네가 알겠지
사무실에서, 내가 오늘 오디션에
가지 않은 이유가 궁금하대
My agent wants to know why I didn't
show up at my audition today...
몇 주만에 들어온 건데
안 전해준 이유가 뭐야?
... my first good one in weeks.
How could you not give me the message?
내가 장난을 좋아하지만...
I'll tell you, I do enjoy guilt...
- 이번엔 나 아니다
- 그래, 네가 맞아
... but it wasn't me.
Yes, it was.
It was him!
그래, 나야!
Okay, it was me!
어떻게 된 거야?
-How was it you?
-Well, it was all so crazy, you know?
너무 정신이 없었어
챈들러가 7까지 셌는데
난 숨을 곳을 못 찾았어
Chandler was in the closet,
counting to 10...
...and I hadn't found a place
to hide yet.
손에 받아 적긴 했어
전부 다
I meant to tell you, and I wrote it all
down on my hand. See? All of it.
- 오디션 전화 맞군
- 그래
Yep, that's my audition.
그래서 난 메모지를
여기저기 붙여놓지
See? Now, this is why I keep
notepads everywhere.
그래서 너희 집이
그렇게 너저분한 거야
Yep. And that's why we don't
invite you to play.
뭐가 그렇게 큰 일이야?
다시 약속을 잡아
What is the great tragedy here?
Get yourself another appointment.
에스텔이 시도해봤는데
감독이 거절했대
Estelle tried. The casting director
told her I missed my chance.
그런 법이 어딨어!
나 때문이라고 전화해줄게
Well, that is unfair!
I'll call her.
I'll tell her it was my fault.
소용없어, 캐스팅 감독은
기획사만 상대하거든
You can't. The casting director
doesn't talk to friends.
-She only talks to agents.
-What a sad little life she must lead.
대인관계가 좁겠구나
좋아
- 뭐 하는 거야? 뭐야?
- 기다려봐
-What are you doing?
-No, I know, I know.
저는 피비 부페이 기획사의
케이틀린입니다
Hi, this is Caitlin
from Phoebe Buffay's office.
앤 좀 바꿔주세요
말하면 다 알 거예요
Is Anne there for Phoebe?
She'll know what it's about.
끊어, 당장!
Hang up. Hang up right
앤, 안녕하세요?
Annie? Hi. Listen, we've got
a problem with Joey Tribbiani.
조이에게 문제가 생겼어요
오디션 시간을 놓쳤대요
Apparently, he missed his audition.
Who did you speak to in my office?
누구한테 말씀하셨죠?
에스텔이요?
걔는 일을 제대로 못해요
Estelle? I don't know
what to do with her.
그러면 남편과 헤어지고
아파트가 불타버렸다구요?
So your husband leaves and burns down
the apartment. The world doesn't stop.
세상 무섭지 않니?
Is anybody else scared?
조이가 오디션을 놓친 건
에스텔 때문이에요
If Joey loses this audition, then
that is it for Estelle. I don't care!
앤, 당신 참 멋져요
Annie, you are a doll. What time can
you see him? I need a pen. Pen!
몇 시가 좋을까요?
펜 좀...
메모지 줘!
메모지!
Get the woman a pad!
Get the woman a pad! A pad! A pad!
Oh, now you want a pad.
메모지가 얼마나
중요한 지 알겠지?
안녕!
우리 아들 왔구나!
우리 아들! 그리고 이건...
Where's my boy?
Here's my boy!
And here's his Barbie!
바비 인형!
얘가 인형을 갖고 놀아?
What's my boy doing with a Barbie?
벤이 직접 고른 장난감이야
너무 좋아해
He picked it out at the store.
He loves it.
늘 갖고 다녀
이게 있어야 안정이 되나봐
He carries it everywhere,
like a security blanket.
장화와 모자도 꼭 입혀서
But with ski boots and a kicky beret.
그래... 귀엽네
그런데 왜...
Yeah, it's cute.
Why does he have it again?
이걸 좋아하지?
인형이 좋다는 데, 문제 있어?
So he's got a doll. So what?
혹시 애가 커서 특이한...
Unless you're afraid
he's gonna grow up to be...
연예인 될까봐?
...in show business.
여자 둘이 키운다고
인형을 좋아하는 건 아냐
This wouldn't have
to do with the fact...
...that he's being raised
by two women?
나도 그쯤은 이해해
인형이 좋다면 할 수 없지
You know what? It's fine. If you're
okay with the Barbie thing, so am l.
아빠한테 인형 줘
이리 줘
Give Daddy the Barbie.
Give me the Barbie.
그럼 이건 어떠니?
괴물 트럭 장난감!
Don't you wanna play
with a monster truck?
싫어? 알았어
No? Okay.
공룡 군인은 어때?
How about a Dino-Soldier?
불쌍하기 그지없네
인형이 어때서 그래?
You are so pathetic.
Why can't your son
just play with his doll?
나 일하러 가야돼
I gotta go to work.
내 가슴패드 본 사람?
Has anybody seen my left boob?
난 저 영화가 좋아
I loved that movie.
내놔, 이걸로 뭐해?
Here it is.
What are you doing?
미안해, 그냥 편해서
I'm sorry. It just felt nice.
조이! 조이!
전화 왔어
Answer the phone.
난 지금 팔이 하나야
나 좀 도와줘, 스웨터 가져와
I only got one arm. You should
do stuff for me. Get me a sweater.
빨리 받아!
Just do it! It's Janice.
이건 제니스야
내가 받으면 만나야 돼
And if I get it, I'll have
to see her tonight.
잘됐군, 만날 수밖에 없네
That's great.
I'll have to see her tonight.
왜 그래?
제니스와 문제 있어?
Why don't you want to see Janice?
어제 저녁을 먹는데
Last night at dinner,
when the meals came...
닭고기 반을 나한테 주고
내 토마토를 다 먹더라구
...she put half her chicken piccata
on my plate and took all my tomatoes.
네가 닭고기를 싫어했었어?
And that's bad...
...because you hate chicken piccata?
아니
토마토를 나눠먹기 싫었으면
그거 참 대단한 토마토네
You didn't want to share your tomatoes.
Tomatoes are very important to you.
아니
애인 사이가 되고부터 이래
Suddenly, we were this "couple."
머리에서 사이렌이 울린다구
And this alarm started going off
in my head.
'살고 싶으면 뛰어!
건물에서 도망쳐'
"Run for your life!
Get out of the building!"
남자들은 정말 이상해
Men are unbelievable.
남자들은 왜 그래?
What is it with you people?
감정이 생기기 시작하는데
도망칠 생각을 해?
The minute you feel something,
you have to run away?
나도 알아...
I know. That
오늘 만나게 되면
뭔가 실수를 할 거 같아
That's why I don't want to go tonight.
I'm afraid I'll say something stupid.
You mean that "guy thing" where
you act mean and distant...
남자들 다 그렇지
'우리 헤어지기 전에
잠깐 거리를 둬보자' 그런거?
... until we break up with you?
- 맞아
- 그걸 알고 있어?
You know about that?
어떻게 하지?
나도 잘 넘기고 싶어
What do I do?
I wanna get past this.
책임이나 약속이 부담스러워
I don't want to be afraid
of commitment.
어두운 터널을 지나
반대쪽으로 나가고 싶어
I want to go through the tunnel
to the other side!
부담이 없는 곳으로
Where there's no fear of commitment.
어떤 방법이...
Do we have any
해결책이 없을까?
Do we have any thoughts here?
난 그런 터널 경험은 없어
I've never been through
the tunnel myself because...
왜냐면, 그런 터널은 여자
한 명만 데리고 가야하거든
...you're not allowed through
with more than one girl in the car.
하지만 모든 것엔
진리라는 답이 있지
But it seems to me it's pretty much
like anything else. Face your fear.
높은 곳이 무서우면
건물 옥상에 올라 가야돼
Fear of heights?
Go to the top of the building.
벌레가 무서우면...
You're afraid of bugs.
벌레를 먹어!
Get a bug.
너 같은 경우는
약속이 부담스러운 거야
You have a fear of commitment.
그러면 약속에 목숨 거는
남자가 되는 거야
So I say you go in there and you be
the most committed guy there ever was!
일리가 있네
Amazingly, that makes sense.
그럴까?
-Do you think?
-Oh, yeah! Go for it, man!
물론이지, 부딪혀봐!
일단 뛰어내리고 보는 거야
Jump off the high dive!
총을 잡고 바람에 맞서
오줌을 갈겨버려!
Stare down the barrel of the gun!
Pee into the wind!
그래?
If I'm staring down
the barrel of a gun...
내가 만일 총을 잡게되면
사방에 오줌을 쌀 거다
...I'm gonna be pretty much peeing
every which way.
CENTRAL
PERK
아침부터 오디션 호출이네
It's your audition from this morning!
- 전화 좀 빌려줄래?
- 그래
Can I use the phone?
Sure, that's what it's there for.
Emergencies and pretend agents.
전화는 이럴 때 써야지
비상시와 가짜 행세할 때
제발, 제발...
Come on, baby! Come on!
호출 받고 전화 드린
피비입니다
Hi. I have Phoebe Buffay
returning a page.
에스텔이 아직 차에 있는데
일단 물어보구요
Okay, she's in her car.
I'll have to patch you through.
아주 잘하고 있어
Very nice touch.
네, 말씀하시죠
Okay, go ahead.
말해, 말해
Talk, talk, talk!
안녕하세요, 앤?
잘 됐네요
Hi, Annie?
Fantastic. You got it!
성공이야!
작은 배역인데 하겠냐구요?
그거야 저는 모르죠
Will he work for scale, you ask me?
Well, I don't know about that.
잘은 몰라도, 할겁니다
Except that I do and he will.
네, 우리 잘 통하네요
저도 함께 식사하고 싶어요
Great. Oh, you are such a sweetheart.
I would love to have lunch with you!
그럼 이번 주 언제...
How about we have lunch next
터널이라 끊겼어
Went through a tunnel.
- 대단하다
- 너무 고마워
Unbelievable.
Oh, thank you so much!
나도 재밌었어!
카폰을 처음 써봤거든
It was really fun. I mean, I've never
talked on a car phone before.
너 대단하다
부탁하나만 들어줄래?
You are so amazing!
Could you do me this huge favor?
좋은 오디션이 하나 있는데
에스텔이 연결을 못해
There's another audition I want,
and Estelle couldn't get me in.
모르겠어
한번은 재밌지만...
I don't know.
It was fun one time, but
제발... 딱 한번만 더!
사실 두 번이지만
Please? It would just be
this one more.
Well, actually it's two.
- 두 번?
- 응!
Two?
솔직히 세 번이야
너 정말 소질 있어
Well, really it's three.
Please? You're so good at it.
I love you.
사랑한다
알았어, 할게
하지만 세 번뿐이다
Okay. But just these three, right?
아니, 네 번
No, it's four.
왜 집에서 식사하자고 했어?
So how come you wanted
to eat in tonight?
왜냐면...
이거 주려고
Because I wanted...
...to give you this.
사랑스런 자기!
Are you a puppy!
인화지?
Contact paper!
데이트하는 남자가 인화지를
주리라곤 꿈도 못 꿨어
What do you say when someone
you're sleeping with...
...gives you contact paper?
또 있어
인화지가 들어갈...
Wait, there's more.
See, the contact paper is to go...
새 서랍!
...in your brand new drawer!
내 장식장에 딱 맞더라
See, the drawer actually
goes in my dresser.
이렇게까지 신경을 쓰다니!
You didn't have to do this.
그래, 신경 써
난 그래
Yes, I did.
Because you're my girlfriend...
넌 내 여자친구이고
원래 이런 대접을 받아야해
...and that's what girlfriends
should get.
내가 무슨 말할지 알지?
Well, I gotta buy a vowel...
이런 세상에!
... because, oh, my God!
Who would've thought that someday...
챈들러가 나에게 서랍을
선물했다는 걸 누가 믿겠어?
... Chandler Bing would buy me
a drawer?
그렇겠지?
Well, not me.
어쨌든 사실이지
한 가지 더 있어
But that's what's happened.
And there's more.
우리 여행 가자
We should take a trip.
- 여행?
- 응
We should?
우린 연인이고
모든 연인이 하는 거지
We're a couple,
and that's what couples do.
그리고 네 부모님도 뵙자
And I wanna meet your parents.
부모님을 모시고
여행을 가는 거야!
We should take a trip
with your parents!
안 가도 될 거 같아
I don't think we need to because
you're tripping me out right now!
자기가 날 비행기 태우고 있어
- 어디 아파?
- 난 괜찮아, 진짜야
Are you okay?
No, I am.
I actually am! This is amazing.
난 이런 순간을 두려워했는데
막상 이 순간 오니까...
My entire life, I have feared
this place.
And now that I'm here, it's like,
what was the big deal?
별 거 아니네!
이런 말도 하고 싶어
'우리 같이 살자! '
I could probably say, "Let's move in
together," and I'd be okay.
정말 같이 살고 싶어?
You probably want us
to move in together?
- 이젠 겁 안 나
- 난 겁나
-lt doesn't scare me!
-Yeah, well it scares me!
난 아직 이혼수속도 안 끝났어
I'm not even divorced yet! You just
invited me over here for pasta...
저녁 먹자고 초대해 놓고
갑자기 같이 살자고 해?
...and now you're talking
about moving in together.
지금 배 안 고파
And I wasn't even that hungry.
늦은 거 같은데, 가야겠어
You know what? It's getting really
late, and I should just
안돼, 가지마! 나도 두려웠어!
내가 너무 심했어?
Don't go! I've scared you!
I've said too much!
난 구제불능이고
사랑에 몸부림치는 놈이야!
I'm hopeless and awkward
and desperate for love!
제니스, 나야
Hey, Janice, it's me.
미리 사과부터 할게
지금 뛰어나가서 잡을 거거든
I wanted to apologize in advance
for having chased you down the street.
또 봐!
이거 먹어,
도움이 될 거야
Here you go, honey. This will help.
뛰어나가서 얘기를 했는데
So I catch up to her
and she says...
우리 관계가 너무 급하다면서
서서히 가까워지재
...this relationship's going too fast
and we have to slow down.
거의 끝났군
That is never good.
내 상태는 현재...
Then I got all...
갈구와 집착 뿐이야
... needy and clingy.
잠깐, 그런 맘이면 괜찮아
제니스는 뭐래?
Wait a minute. Maybe it's
not so bad. How did you leave it?
나중에 전화한대
She said she'd call me.
하느님!
Oh, God.
여자 터널로 온 거 환영해
Welcome to our side of the tunnel.
아이스크림 맛이 형편없어
This ice cream tastes like crap,
by the way.
저 칼로리 두유로
만들어서 그래
Well, it's that
low-cal-nondairy-soymilk junk.
맛있는 건 종점에
가서 먹는 거야
We save the real stuff
for the truly terminal cases.
When you're getting screwed over all
the time, you gotta switch to low fat.
일이 꼬이기 시작할 때
먹는 건 저 칼로리가 좋아
맞아
Yeah, you do.
그럼 난 종점이 아냐?
You don't think I'm terminal?
아니지, 종점은 아냐
상처를 살펴봐야지
Not at all. You're not terminal.
We just need some damage control.
알았어, 그럼 전화할까?
Okay. Should I call her?
안돼!
It's a critical time. If you feel
yourself reaching for that phone...
지금이 아주 중요한 시기야
전화하고 싶어지면 쇼핑을 가
아니면 목욕을 하던지
...go shopping, get your butt
in a bubble bath.
제니스를 돌아오게 하려면
무관심한 척 해야돼
If you want her back,
you have got to start acting aloof.
갈구하는 모습을
보이면 안돼
She has to know you're not needy.
이제 남은 건...
So what you have to do is...
그녀와 우연히 마주친 척 하고,
담담한 척해
...you have to accidentally
run into her on purpose...
...and then act aloof.
그럼 잃지 않는 거지?
So I'm not gonna lose her?
당연히 인생은 잃지 않아
Oh, honey, you're not a total loser.
내 인생 말고, 여자 말야
I said, "So I'm not gonna lose her?"
이게 누구게? 장난감 나라에서
제일 터프한 사나이야
Guess who's here!
It's the toughest guy in Toyland, Ben!
진정한 미국의 영웅
지 아이 조!
Real American hero
I'm G.I. Joe!
인형 내려놔, 버려!
Drop the Barbie. Drop the Barbie.
지 아이 조?
애가 그걸 좋아할 거 같아?
G.I. Joe?
You really think he'll fall for that?
지 아이 조?
같이 놀자
G.I. Joe?
Cool! Can I play?
이건 중동의 석유를
지켜주는 장난감이야
Look, Ben! It's a toy that protects
U.S. oil interests overseas!
가자, 조!
Go, Joe!
안녕!
피비, 왔구나
-There you are!
-No, it's not. Sorry.
- 잘 못 왔어, 미안
- 피비, 잠깐만
But, Phoebe, wait, wait.
Phoebe!
조이구나! 네가 바지를
갈아입어서 못 알아봤어
Oh, Joey! Oh, okay!
See, I didn't recognize you...
...in those pants.
텔레비전 영화 오디션 결과
들었어? 느낌이 좋았는데
That TV movie I went in for,
did you hear anything?
I think I got a shot at it.
응, 들었어, 떨어졌어
Yes, they called!
You didn't get it!
떨어졌어... 미안해
Okay? I mean, you didn't get it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
괜찮아, 늘 있는 일이야
That's okay. These things happen.
이건 말도 안돼
너 이거 아니?
But they shouldn't happen.
You know what?
네가 있는 연예계는
너무 힘든 곳이야
You're in a terrible,
terrible business.
네 표정을 이렇게
만든 내가 싫어
I don't want to be the person
who makes you look like that.
난 괜찮아, 봐?
I'm okay. See?
그게 더 불쌍해 보여
Now you're sad and creepy.
미안해, 이제 관둘래
I'm sorry. I quit.
안돼, 그만 두지마!
넌 최고의 에이전시야
No, no, you can't quit!
You're the best agent I ever had.
배우는 거절당하면서 성장해
네 책임이 아냐
Rejection is part of being an actor.
You can't take it personal.
그래? 정말?
They said they'd never met an ltalian
actor with a worse ltalian accent.
그 사람들이 너한테, 발음도
제대로 못하는 배우라고 했어
진짜 그랬어?
They actually said that?
세상에, 네 표정 좀 봐!
난 못해, 마음이 아파...
Oh, God, there's that face again.
See? I can't do this job!
아냐, 그래서 네가
이 일을 해야되는 거야
This is why
you have to do this job!
기획사는 거짓말도 해
Agents always lie.
에스텔은 이런 식으로 해
다른 쪽으로 갔어요
Estelle just says stuff like,
"They went another way."
난 그런 것도 괜찮아
But this? I can use this.
발음을 워떻게든 고쳐 볼껴
I can work on a new accent.
그래, 알았어
그러면 되겠지
Yeah, okay. If it
helps you, okay. Yeah.
넌 날 절대 못 잡아, 조!
You'll never get me, Joe!
아뇨, 됐어요
No, thank you.
챈들러?
안녕, 제니스
여긴 웬일이야?
What are you doing here?
쇼핑하러 왔지
잘 지냈어?
Just a bit of shopping.
How have you been?
말투가 왜 그래?
Are you being British?
일부러 하는 거 아냐
Not anymore.
이 동네 사람도 아니면서
왜 여기서 쇼핑해?
Why are you shopping here?
You don't live in this neighborhood.
날 기다린 거야?
Were you here waiting for me?
그럴 리가!
파티 때문에 온 거야
I'm just...
... picking up some things for a party.
보리?
Barley?
무슨 파티인데
보리차가 필요해?
What kind of party serves barley?
미안, 친구들 기호식품이
워낙 특이해 놔서
I'm sorry if my friends aren't
as sophisticated as yours.
어디서 파티하는데?
Where is this party?
여기 첼시에서
Here in Chelsea.
누가 주최하는데?
Whose party is it?
여자
A woman's.
어떤 여자?
What woman?
첼시
Chelsea.
분명 둘 중 하나군
Either you're seeing somebody
behind my back...
나 몰래 여자를 만난다면
세상 최고의 바보인 거고
...which would make you
the world's biggest jerk...
여자를 만나는 척
하는 거라면
...or you're pretending
to see somebody...
난 마음이 아픈 나머지
식료품코너에서 울어버릴 거야
...which makes you so pathetic
I could cry right here!
둘 중에 어떤 남자인 거야?
So which of these two guys
do you want to be?
거기에 껴주는 거야?
Can I be that guy?
거절을 많이 당했으니까
이유를 파악해야돼
Okay, we got some more good
rejections. Lots of stuff to work on.
그래, 하자
Okay. Shoot.
그래... 동물원 광고주!
Okay. Oh, the zoo commercial.
- 그것도 거절당했어?
- 그래
I didn't get it?
광고주가 널 인간으로
볼 수 없다고 했으니까
They said that you
"weren't believable as a human being."
이건 가능하겠어
So you can work on that.
Great.
다른 건?
What else?
연극 연출자들이
넌 '미남에, 멍청이'래
The off-Broadway-play people said
that you were "pretty but dumb."
다시 보니까
'미련한 멍청이'네
Oh, no wait. I'm sorry.
That's "pretty dumb."
알았어, 됐어
Look, it's okay, no, no, no.
Really.
네가 도와주는 게 고맙긴 한데
그냥 에스텔한테 갈게
Look...
... I really appreciate this...
... but I'm gonna have to
go back to Estelle.
오해는 하지마
네가 그 여자보다 나아
Don't get me wrong.
You're a better agent than she is...
하지만 네 얘길 듣고 있으면
머리를 쥐어뜯고 싶어져
... but at least with her, I don't want
to blow my pretty dumb brains out.
응, 이해해
Yeah, no, I understand.
- 정말?
- 응
You do? Thanks. Okay.
- 고마워
- 미안해
Sorry.
- 잠깐만
- 왜?
Wait a minute.
기획사 일 하기 싫어서
다 꾸며낸 얘기들이지?
Wait a minute.
Did you make all that stuff up
to get out of being my agent?
들켰네
Oh, he caught me.
뭘 해도 티가 나
I am so busted!
어째 미심쩍다 했어
That's what I suspected!
그래서 보리를 제니스한테
던지고 뛰어나왔어
And then I just, you know...
...threw the bag of barley at her
and ran out of the store.
덤덤하라고 했지
던지라고 했니?
My God, Chandler, we said be "aloof,"
not "a doof."
내가 다 망친 거지?
I've actually ruined this, haven't l?
맛있는 아이스크림
먹을 때가 됐니?
Is it time for the good ice cream now?
가져올게
Yeah, it is.
다 괜찮아 질 거야
You know what?
Everything's gonna be okay.
여보세요?
안녕, 제니스
잠깐 기다릴래?
Can you hold on for a second?
이제 뭐라고 하지?
What do I do?
몰라, 예상치 못한 거야
I don't know.
This is unprecedented.
우리가 너처럼 했으면
남자는 전화 안 해
If we did what you did,
a man would never call.
- 그럼 어쩌라구?
- 그래, 이렇게 해!
I got it! Pretend you just woke up.
That'll throw her off!
잠에서 막 깬 것처럼 해
그럼 실망할 거야
- 졸린 척!
- 그리고 화난 척!
-Be sleepy!
-Yes! And grumpy!
그놈의 척, 척 좀 그만 해!
What are you?
Stop naming dwarfs!
제니스, 안녕
전화 줘서 고마워
I'm so glad that you called.
내가 요즘 행동이 이상했지?
I know I've been acting
really weird lately...
그건 자길 너무나 사랑하기
때문이야
...and it's just because
I'm crazy about you...
두려워서...
멍청하게 행동했어
...and I just got stupid and scared...
...and stupid a couple more times.
미안해
And I'm sorry.
정말?
Really?
정말이지?
남자는 좋겠다
He's so lucky.
If Janice were a guy...
제니스가 남자였으면
벌써 다른 여자를 만났을걸
...she'd be sleeping
with somebody else by now.
나도 사랑해
I love you too.
It's so unfair!
너무 불공평해
지 아이 조?
G. I. Joe? G. I. Joe?!
뭐라 설명하긴 힘들지만
애가 고른 거야
I don't know what to tell you guys.
That's the doll he chose.
설탕이라도 묻혀서 줬어?
What'd you do, dip it in sugar?
지 아이 조, 세이프
바비 인형, 아웃
Look, G. I. Joe's in, Barbie's out.
And if you guys can't deal with it,
that's just your too bad.
그걸 인정할 수 없다면
당신 둘이 문제인 거야
왜 억지로 바꾸려고 해?
인형 좋아하는 게 대수야?
What are you being such a weenie for?
So he has a Barbie. Big deal.
오빠도 여자 옷 입는 거
좋아했잖아
You used to dress up like a woman.
뭐?
What?
맨날 엄마 옷 꺼내 입고
그랬잖아
The way you used to dress up
in Mom's clothes?
그게 무슨 소리야?
What are you talking about?
챙 넓은 모자, 진주 목걸이에
분홍색 가방...
The big hat, the pearls,
the little pink handbag?
괜히 말 꾸미지마
Okay. You are totally
making this up.
오빠 기억 안 나?
'비'라고 불러 달랬던 거!
How can you not remember?
You made us call you "Bea"?
이런...
Oh, God.
이런 동질감을 느끼긴
처음이야
I've literally never been this happy.
노래도 불렀잖아
Wasn't there a little song?
어서 불러봐
Oh, please, God,
let there be a song.
그런 건 정말 없었어
진짜 없었어
There was no song.
- '난 비예요'
- 알았다
I am Bea
- '난 차를 마셔요'
- 알았어, 그만해라
-I drink tea
-That's enough.
'어서 나와... 나와서... '
Won't you....
어서 나와서 나랑 춤출래요?
Won't you dance around with me?
'난 비예요, 난 차를 마셔요
어서 나와서 나랑 춤출래요?'
I am Bea
I drink tea
Won't you dance around with?
오빠?
Ross?